Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Denis Lanigan papers, 1955-1986 RL.00699
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- New York Office, 1970-1986; 1
  - J. Walter Thompson, 1955-1986; 1
    - Goals and objectives, 1981-1983 (Box 13)
    - Greece--Spot Thompson, 1980-1983 (Box 13)
    - Growth statement, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Hong Kong, 1985 (Box 13)
    - India, 1984-1986 (Box 13)
    - James Heekin, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Japan, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Japan, Korea, 1985 (Box 14)
    - Latin America--Managers Meeting, 1981-1984; 4 folders (Box 14)
    - Latin America--Operational Review, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Latin America--Propaganda Magazine, 1982 (Box 14)
    - Letters to retiring staff, 1985 (Box 14)
    - London Office (includes Europe materials), 1980 (Box 14)
    - London Office (includes Europe materials), 1981-1982; 7 folders (Box 15)
    - London Office (includes Europe materials), 1983-1985; 8 folders (Box 16)
    - London Office (includes Europe materials), 1981 (Box 48)
    - London Office--David Holmes, 1985 (Box 17)
    - London Office--Europe research, 1981; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - London Office--Ian Bruce, John Lindsay-Bethune, 1981 (Box 17)
    - London Office--Research, 1978 (Box 17)
    - London Office--Restrictions on Transfer of Advertising Material Between Countries, 1983 (Box 17)
    - London Office--Stock options, 1984-1985 (Box 17)
    - London Office--Stock purchase plans, 1982 (Box 17)
    - London Office--Survival Anglia, 1981 (Box 48)
    - London Office--The Case for Advertising, 1975-1976 (Box 48)
    - London Office--Trip, 1983 (Box 17)
    - Lord Geller Federico Einstein, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Management Development Program (Troutbeck), 1982-1983; 5 folders (Box 17)
    - Management Development Program (Troutbeck), 1982-1983; 3 folders (Box 18)
    - (Management Information Systems) MIS Coordinating Committee, 1981 (Box 18)
    - (Management Information Systems) MIS Steering Committee, 1982 (Box 18)
    - Manila, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Media, 1982-1984 (Box 18)
    - Memos, 1983-1986; 4 folders (Box 18)
    - Mexico City, 1980-1983 (Box 18)
    - Mexico Creative Forum, 1983 (Box 19)
    - Mexico Earthquake, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Monitoring Group, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Morgan Stanley, 1983 (Box 19)
    - Multinational Client Services, 1983 (Box 19)
    - New York Office pep rally, 1983 (Box 19)
    - News, 1984-1986 (Box 19)
    - Operations Committee, 1982-1984; 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Personnel--Compensation, 1981-1982 (Box 19)
    - Personnel--Drinks with Denis, 1983 (Box 19)
    - Personnel--Employee Attitude Surveys (includes Australia, Canada), 1980-1981; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Personnel--Employee benefits, 1981-1984; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Personnel--Management change, 1982 (Box 20)
    - Personnel--Management succession, 1986 (Box 20)
    - Personnel--Marketing plan for recruitment, 1982 (Box 20)
    - Personnel--Recruitment, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Personnel--Retired Directors, 1984-1985 (Box 20)
    - Personnel--Retirement seminar, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Personnel--"Stars and Keepers" retention ideas, 1981 (Box 20)
    - Philosophy of JWT, 1955-1983 (Box 20)
    - Philosophy of JWT, 1955-1983 (Box 21)
    - Rena Bartos--Communications Plan, 1982 (Box 21)
    - Rena Bartos--Speakers program (English and Spanish), 1980 (Box 21)
    - Rena Bartos--Speakers program Chile (Spanish), 1980 (Box 48)
    - Saatchi & Saatchi, 1984-1986 (Box 21)
    - Saatchi & Saatchi, 1984-1986 (Box 48)
    - Sam Meek, 1981-1984 (Box 21)
    - Sam Meek Seminar, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Sample letter of terms, 1981 (Box 21)
    - San Francisco, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Seminars, 1983-1986 (Box 22)
    - Seminars and meetings, 1980-1985 (Box 22)
    - SMRB/MRI (market research firms), 1982-1983 (Box 22)
    - Thailand (English and Thai), 1984 (Box 22)
    - "The Plan" (Thompson Plan) Task Force, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Thompson Recruitment, 1982-1986; 3 folders (Box 22)
    - Turkey, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
    - USA administration correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 23)
    - Wall Street Transcript, 1981 (Box 23)
    - Washington, 1980-1981 (Box 23)
  - JWT Group, 1980-1986; 2
    - Annual meeting, 1981-1984; 4 folders (Box 23)
    - Annual report, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
    - Banking and borrowing policy, 1980-1982 (Box 23)
    - Board meetings, 1983-1985 (Box 23)
    - Chairman's letter, 1983-1984 (Box 23)
    - Chairman's meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 23)
    - Chairman's meetings, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Corporate communications, 1981-1985 (Box 24)
    - Data processing study, 1980-1983; 3 folders (Box 24)
    - Europe reports, 1982 (Box 24)
    - Expense policy, 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Goals and objectives, 1981-1983 (Box 24)
    - Goals and objectives, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Growth statement, 1982 (Box 25)
    - London Stock Exchange listing, 1983 (Box 25)
    - Press review, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Review, 1981 (Box 25)
    - Security Analysts presentation, 1980-1981 (Box 25)
    - SMRB report to Board, 1985 (Box 25)
    - Worldwide Managers Meeting, 1980 (Box 25)
  - Chronological Files, 1979-1986; 3
    - 1979 Feb.-1980 May, 3 folders (Box 25)
    - 1980 June-1981 Jan., 8 folders (Box 26)
    - 1981 Feb.-July, 6 folders (Box 27)
    - 1981 Aug.-1982 Feb., 8 folders (Box 28)
    - 1982 Mar.-July, 7 folders (Box 29)
    - 1982 Aug.-Dec., 6 folders (Box 30)
    - 1983 Jan.-June, 8 folders (Box 31)
    - 1983 June-Oct., 6 folders (Box 32)
    - 1983 Oct.-1984 Feb., 6 folders (Box 33)
    - 1984 Feb.-July, 6 folders (Box 34)
    - 1984 July-1985 Jan., 6 folders (Box 35)
    - 1985 Feb.-July, 6 folders (Box 36)
    - 1985 Aug.-1986 Feb., 7 folders (Box 37)
    - 1986 Mar.-Dec., 6 folders (Box 38)
  - Account Files, 1975-1985; 4
    - Chevron, 1982, 1985; 2 folders (Box 38)
    - Close-Up presentation (London), 1983 (Box 38)
    - Kellogg, 1980-1983; 3 folders (Box 39)
    - Kodak, 1980-1984; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Kraft, 1981-1982; 5 folders (Box 39)
    - Kraft, 1981-1984; 6 folders (Box 40)
    - Kraft--Michael Miles visit, 1983 (Box 40)
    - London--Central Office of Information (Nuclear arms campaign), 1983 (Box 40)
    - Nestle, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Pepsi, 1982-1983; 3 folders (Box 41)
    - Price Waterhouse, 1983 (Box 41)
    - R.J. Reynolds, 1981-1983; 4 folders (Box 41)
    - Red Cross, 1982 (Box 41)
    - Unilever, 1980-1981; 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Unilever, 1981-1984; 8 folders (Box 42)
    - Unilever--Account review, 1983 (Box 43)
    - Unilever--Billings and profits, 1981-1983; 3 folders (Box 43)
    - Unilever--Brian Roberts-Wray, 1984 (Box 43)
    - Unilever--Conflict policy, 1979-1983 (Box 43)
    - Unilever--Detergents coordination, 1984 (Box 43)
    - Unilever--Hair care strategy, 1981 (Box 43)
    - Unilever--Latin America presentation, 1983 (Box 43)
    - Unilever--Overseas Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 43)
    - Unilever--Presentation, 1984 (Box 43)
    - Unilever--Press seminar, 1982 (Box 43)
    - Unilever--Remuneration, 1975-1984 (Box 43)
    - Unilever--Sir David Orr, 1982 (Box 43)
    - Unilever--Supervisors conference, 1981-1983; 2 folders (Box 44)
  - Speeches and Presentations, 1970-1986; 5
    - 1985 Plan, 1984 (Box 44)
    - Advertising Wars--Hong Kong version, 1985 (Box 44)
    - Atlanta, 1984 (Box 44)
    - Australia, 1984 (Box 44)
    - Bangkok, 1984 (Box 44)
    - Broadcast Television and the New Electronic Media (Tuula Piispanen), 1983 (Box 44)
    - Brouillard/Canada, 1985 (Box 44)
    - Canada, 1984 (Box 44)
    - Capetown, 1984 (Box 44)
    - Don Johnston presentation to Canada staff, 1983 (Box 44)
    - Europe, 1984 (Box 44)
    - Europe--EROC presentation, 1985 (Box 44)
    - European visit, 1984 (Box 44)
    - Future's Not What It Used to Be, 1983 (Box 44)
    - Helsinki, 1985 (Box 45)
    - Hill & Knowlton, 1985 (Box 45)
    - Impact of Telecommunications on Advertising, 1982 (Box 45)
    - India, Dubai, 1986 (Box 45)
    - J. Walter Thompson International Overview (William E. Ross), 1980 (Box 45)
    - Jim Agnew/Los Angeles Office, 1985 (Box 45)
    - John Sharman presentation, 1970-1976 (Box 45)
    - JWT Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 45)
    - JWT Frankfurt presentation, 1980 (Box 45)
    - JWT Group Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 45)
    - Kuala Lumpur, 1984 (Box 45)
    - Latin America Peer Review, 1985 (Box 45)
    - Latin American Managers Meeting, 1984 (Box 45)
    - Manila--Asia Pacific Managers Meeting, 1985 (Box 45)
    - Marketing in the World Village, 1982 (Box 46)
    - Miscellaneous speeches, 1982 (Box 46)
    - Multinational presentation, 1985 (Box 46)
    - New York Professional Development Group, 1984 (Box 46)
    - New Zealand, 1984 (Box 46)
    - Operations Committee, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Peer review, 1985 (Box 46)
    - Planning review, 1985; 2 folders (Box 46)
    - San Francisco, 1985 (Box 46)
    - San Francisco--State of the Agency (Frank Mainero), 1982 (Box 46)
    - Security Analysts presentation, 1983 (Box 46)
    - Singapore, 1984 (Box 46)
    - Speech schedule, 1982 (Box 46)
    - Strategic Review--Executive Committee, 1985 (Box 46)
    - Strategic Review--JWT Group, 1985 (Box 47)
    - Strategic Review--Morgan Stanley, 1985 (Box 47)
    - Strategic Review--New York Financial Group, 1985 (Box 47)
    - Thompson Recruitment--JWT profile, 1986 (Box 47)
    - Tokyo, Hong Kong, 1985 (Box 47)
    - Troutbeck, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 47)
    - World Agency Competitive Review 1984 vs. 1974, 1985 (Box 47)
    - Worldwide Client Service Directors, 1984 (Box 47)
    - Worldwide Client Services, 1985 (Box 47)